<ORGANIZATION>Baker International Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it has signed a definitive agreement to sell the assets and business of the electric submersible oilwell pump product line in the continental <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> of its <ORGANIZATION>Baker Oil Tools Inc</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary to <ORGANIZATION>Trico Industries Inc TRO</ORGANIZATION> for an undisclosed amount of cash and other consideration .
The company said the transaction is subject to <ORGANIZATION>Hughes Tool Co HT</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Baker</ORGANIZATION> shareholder approval of the <ORGANIZATION>Baker/Hughes</ORGANIZATION> merger .
The <ORGANIZATION>U.S. Justice Department</ORGANIZATION> has announced that it will require divestiture of the product line for approval of the merger .
<ORGANIZATION>Baker</ORGANIZATION> said the transaction is subject to approval by the <ORGANIZATION>Justice Department</ORGANIZATION> and the boards of <ORGANIZATION>Baker</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Hughes</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Trico</ORGANIZATION> .
