<ORGANIZATION>Caremark Inc</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Baxter Travenol Laboratories Inc</ORGANIZATION> jointly announced that <ORGANIZATION>Caremark</ORGANIZATION> shareholders will vote on July 31 to approve the previously announced merger with <ORGANIZATION>Baxter</ORGANIZATION> .
The companies said <ORGANIZATION>Caremark</ORGANIZATION> shareholders of record as of June 26 will be entitled to vote at the meeting to be held in <LOCATION>Newport Beach</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Calif</LOCATION> , at 1000 PDT .
On May 11 , <ORGANIZATION>Baxter</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Carmark</ORGANIZATION> announced a definitive agreement for <ORGANIZATION>Baxter</ORGANIZATION> to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Carmark</ORGANIZATION> in a stock transaction valued at 528 mln dlrs .
