<ORGANIZATION>Allegheny International Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it and <ORGANIZATION>First Boston Inc</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>FBC Sunter Holdings Corp</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary have been named as defendants in a class action filed in the <ORGANIZATION>Court of Common Pleas</ORGANIZATION> for <LOCATION>Allegheny County</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Pa.</LOCATION> , which seeks an injunction against <ORGANIZATION>Allegheny</ORGANIZATION> 's proposed merger into <ORGANIZATION>Sunter</ORGANIZATION> .
The company said its board and some former directors and <ORGANIZATION>First Boston</ORGANIZATION> were also named as defendants .
It said it and <PERSON>Sunter</PERSON> intend to vigorously oppose the action .
<ORGANIZATION>Allegheny</ORGANIZATION> said the class action suit alleges the price to be paid in the transaction is grossly unfair .
The company said the suit 's allegations are similar to those contained in an earlier federal court suit .
