<ORGANIZATION>Fidelity National Financial Inc</ORGANIZATION> said its <ORGANIZATION>Fidelity National Title Insurance Co</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary acquired the operations of <ORGANIZATION>Safeco Title Insurance Co</ORGANIZATION> in the <LOCATION>northern California</LOCATION> counties of <LOCATION>Alameda</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Contra Costa</ORGANIZATION> and <LOCATION>San Mateo</LOCATION> .
Terms of the acquisition were not disclosed .
