<ORGANIZATION>Unicorp Canada Corp</ORGANIZATION> told the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> it cut its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Purolator Courier Corp</ORGANIZATION> to 286,500 shares , or 3.7 pct of the total outstanding , from 962,400 shares , or 12.4 pct .
<ORGANIZATION>Unicorp</ORGANIZATION> , a management and investment holding company controlled by its chairman , <PERSON>George Mann</PERSON> , said it sold 675,900 <ORGANIZATION>Purolator</ORGANIZATION> common shares on March 2 and 3 at 3</DATE>4.782 and 3</DATE>4.750 dlrs a share .
Purolator agreed this past weekend to be acquired by managers of its <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> courier business and <ORGANIZATION>E.F. Hutton LBO Inc</ORGANIZATION> in a leveraged buyout valued at 265 mln dlrs .
