<ORGANIZATION>National Distillers and Chemical Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it completed the sale of <ORGANIZATION>Almaden Vineyards Inc</ORGANIZATION> to <ORGANIZATION>Heublein Inc</ORGANIZATION> for about 128 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Heublein</ORGANIZATION> , a former subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>RJR Nabisco Inc RJR</ORGANIZATION> , was recently acquired by <ORGANIZATION>Grand Metropolitan PLC.</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Almaden</ORGANIZATION> , based in <LOCATION>San Jose</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Calif.</LOCATION> , makes and sells table wines , champagnes and brandies as well as some premium wines under the <ORGANIZATION>Charles Lefranc Cellars</ORGANIZATION> label .
