An appeal by <ORGANIZATION>Buitoni SpA</ORGANIZATION> against a court ruling that an accord under which it was to acquire Italian state food firm <ORGANIZATION>SME</ORGANIZATION> - <ORGANIZATION>Societa Meridionale Finanziaria</ORGANIZATION> was not contractually binding has been rejected , court officials said .
An appeal court rejected <ORGANIZATION>Buitoni</ORGANIZATION> 's claim that the 497 billion lire accord with the state industrial company <ORGANIZATION>IRI</ORGANIZATION> - <ORGANIZATION>Istituto per la Ricostruzione Industriale</ORGANIZATION> was a binding contract .
The decision upholds a court ruling of last July .
<ORGANIZATION>Buitoni</ORGANIZATION> is controlled by <ORGANIZATION>CIR</ORGANIZATION> - <ORGANIZATION>Compagnie Industriali Riunite</ORGANIZATION> , an investment company itself controlled by <ORGANIZATION>Ing C Olivetti EC SpA</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>OLIV.MI</ORGANIZATION> > chairman <PERSON>Carlo De Benedetti</PERSON> .
