Malaysia 's national oil company , <ORGANIZATION>Petronas</ORGANIZATION> , has advised the government to raise crude oil output to 540,000 barrels a day ( bpd ) in 1988 from a current 500,000 bpd , a senior company official said .
" We have the capacity to produce the amount , " <PERSON>Rastam Hadi</PERSON> , <ORGANIZATION>Petronas</ORGANIZATION> 's Vice-President for <ORGANIZATION>Upstream Sector</ORGANIZATION> said .
The government will announce its decision on Friday when it unveils the country 's budget .
<LOCATION>Malaysia</LOCATION> raised output this month to current levels from 420,000 bpd after reviewing the world oil market .
In May , <LOCATION>Malaysia</LOCATION> cut output to 420,000 bpd from 459,000 in response to a call by <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> to boost prices .
