<ORGANIZATION>Nusource Investments Inc</ORGANIZATION> , a publicly held shell company , said it acquired <ORGANIZATION>American Nutrition Works Inc</ORGANIZATION> through a transaction in which <ORGANIZATION>American Nutrition</ORGANIZATION> shareholders received 28 mln shares of <ORGANIZATION>Nusource</ORGANIZATION> stock in exchange for their shares .
<ORGANIZATION>American Nutrition</ORGANIZATION> operates a chain of stores sellings vitamins and health products .
<ORGANIZATION>Nusource</ORGANIZATION> said shareholders elected a new board consisting of <PERSON>Richard A. Trydahl</PERSON> , <PERSON>Samuel Mineo</PERSON> and <PERSON>Charles E. Flink</PERSON> and voted to change the name of the company to <ORGANIZATION>ANW Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
