<ORGANIZATION>General Electric Co Plc</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>GECL.L</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>GEC </ORGANIZATION> ) declined comment on rumours on the <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> stock market that it is planning another purchase in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Medical equipment field , in addition to its existing <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Subsidiary < <ORGANIZATION>Picker International Inc</ORGANIZATION> > .
A <ORGANIZATION>GEC</ORGANIZATION> spokesman said that it is company policy not to comment on acquisition rumours .
<ORGANIZATION>Stock Exchange</ORGANIZATION> traders said the rumour helped <ORGANIZATION>GEC</ORGANIZATION> 's share price to rise 5p , to a final 206p from yesterday 's closing price of 201p .
