<ORGANIZATION>Hollinger Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it completed the previously reported acquisition of privately held <ORGANIZATION>Unimedia Inc</ORGANIZATION> , the owner of three French language daily newspapers and four printing plants in <LOCATION>Ontario</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Quebec</LOCATION> .
The company , which owns 58 pct of ( <ORGANIZATION>Daily Telegraph Plc</ORGANIZATION> ) said it named former <ORGANIZATION>Carling O'Keefe Ltd</ORGANIZATION> chief executive <PERSON>Pierre Des Marais</PERSON> as chief executive of <ORGANIZATION>La Societe Media Quebec</ORGANIZATION> , the unit acquiring <ORGANIZATION>Unimedia</ORGANIZATION> .
It said his appointment is effective July 2 .
