<ORGANIZATION>Siemens AG</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>SIEG.F</ORGANIZATION> fully-owned subsidiary <ORGANIZATION>Siemens Informations Systems Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
Has raised its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Telecom Plus Communications Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
By 65 pct to 100 pct , a <ORGANIZATION>Siemens</ORGANIZATION> spokesman said .
He added that <ORGANIZATION>Telecom Plus Communications</ORGANIZATION> was the largest independent supplier of telephone exchange systems in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> And had achieved a turnover of 234 mln dlrs in 1986 .
The stake had been acquired from <ORGANIZATION>Telecom Plus International Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
The spokesman declined to comment on <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Newspaper reports that the purchase price of the remaining stake totalled 173 mln dlrs .
