<ORGANIZATION>Hudson Valley Patrol Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to acquire privately held <ORGANIZATION>Federal Protection Services Inc</ORGANIZATION> , a <LOCATION>Palm Beach</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Fla.</LOCATION> , security firm , for 200,000 common shares and other considerations .
<ORGANIZATION>Hudson Valley</ORGANIZATION> , which provides guard and patrol services in <LOCATION>upstate N.Y.</LOCATION> , said <ORGANIZATION>Federal Protection Services</ORGANIZATION> provides investigation , uniformed guard and armoured truck services to banks , corporations and residential communities in southern <LOCATION>Florida</LOCATION> .
The company said it will issue 200,000 shares of its common at closing and additional shares based on <ORGANIZATION>Federal Protection</ORGANIZATION> 's pretax earnings over the next three years .
Closing is subject to setting a definitive agreement , it said .
