<ORGANIZATION>General Electric Co</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>GE Credit Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to buy all of the capital stock of <ORGANIZATION>Kraft Inc</ORGANIZATION> 's wholly owned subsidiary <ORGANIZATION>D and K Financial Corp.</ORGANIZATION> .
Terms of the acquisition were not disclosed .
<ORGANIZATION>D and K</ORGANIZATION> , with assets of more than one billion dlrs , is one of the leading <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> companies involved in the leasing of fleets of cars , according to <ORGANIZATION>GE Credit</ORGANIZATION> .
<PERSON>Jim Ahtes</PERSON> , a spokesman for <ORGANIZATION>GE Credit</ORGANIZATION> 's outside public relations firm , <ORGANIZATION>Manning , Selvage and Lee Inc</ORGANIZATION> , emphasized that the terms of the acquisition had not yet been approved .
