<ORGANIZATION>Century Communications Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it had entered into an agreement to acquire all the assets of <ORGANIZATION>Community Cable Vision of Puerto Rico Associates</ORGANIZATION> and its associated companies for about 12 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Century</ORGANIZATION> said it anticipates that <ORGANIZATION>ML Media Partners LP</ORGANIZATION> , which jointly owns with <ORGANIZATION>Century</ORGANIZATION> a company called < <ORGANIZATION>Cable Television Co</ORGANIZATION> > of greater <LOCATION>San Juan</LOCATION> , will join in acquisition and management of <ORGANIZATION>Community Cable</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Century</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Community Cable</ORGANIZATION> is located in <LOCATION>San Juan</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Puerto Rico</LOCATION> .
