President <PERSON>Nobuo Ito</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>International Telecom Japan Inc</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>ITJ</ORGANIZATION> ) , one of two rival firms seeking to enter <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> 's international telecommunications market , said it will offer a stake in the company to 10 foreign firms .
But he declined to specify what share the firms would take , and told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> they would not participate in its management .
<ORGANIZATION>ITJ</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>International Digital Communications Planning Inc</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>IDC</ORGANIZATION> ) , in which both <ORGANIZATION>Cable and Wireless Plc</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Pacific Telesis Group</ORGANIZATION> own 20 pct stakes , are set to merge into a new entity to compete against <ORGANIZATION>Kokusai Denshin Denwa Co Ltd.</ORGANIZATION> .
