<ORGANIZATION>Ranger Oil Ltd</ORGANIZATION> said it completed on March 2 the previously announced sale of its <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> oil and gas properties held by subsidiaries <ORGANIZATION>Ranger Oil Co</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Ranger Inc</ORGANIZATION> to <ORGANIZATION>Ampol Exploration Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , of <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION> , for 18.5 mln <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Ranger</ORGANIZATION> said that under the deal , it would retain a five pct gross overriding royalty on its stake from blocks east cameron 65 and 82 in the <LOCATION>Gulf of Mexico</LOCATION> offshore <LOCATION>Lousiana</LOCATION> .
It said the sale did not include <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> properties acquired from <ORGANIZATION>Berkeley Exploration and Production PLC</ORGANIZATION> last December .
