A subsidiary of state energy concern <ORGANIZATION>Ente Nazionali Idrocarburi</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>ENTN.MI</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>ENI</ORGANIZATION> ) said it has acquired a 50 pct stake in <ORGANIZATION>Steuart Petroleum Co</ORGANIZATION> , an independent <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Oil products company .
Financial terms were not disclosed .
<ORGANIZATION>Agip Petroli Spa</ORGANIZATION> said in a statement that the remaining 50 pct of the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Firm is owned by <ORGANIZATION>Steuart Investment Co</ORGANIZATION> , a holding company which also has interests transportation , hotels and insurance .
The Italian firm said <ORGANIZATION>Steuart Petroleum</ORGANIZATION> operates primarily on the <LOCATION>East Coast of the U.S.</LOCATION> .
