<ORGANIZATION>KLM Royal Dutch Airlines KLM.A</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to take a 15 pct stake in <ORGANIZATION>Air U.K. Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , a subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>British and Commonwealth Shipping Plc BCOM.L</ORGANIZATION> , in a transaction worth around two mln stg .
A <ORGANIZATION>KLM</ORGANIZATION> spokesman said <ORGANIZATION>KLM</ORGANIZATION> already cooperated closely with <ORGANIZATION>Air UK</ORGANIZATION> , which runs 111 flights a week to <LOCATION>Amsterdam</LOCATION> 's <LOCATION>Schipol airport</LOCATION> from nine UK cities .
<ORGANIZATION>British and Commonwealth Shipping</ORGANIZATION> said last week it held preliminary talks about a <ORGANIZATION>KLM</ORGANIZATION> minority stake in <LOCATION>Air U.K.</LOCATION> .
But gave no further details .
<ORGANIZATION>KLM</ORGANIZATION> said it hoped the move would attract more British feeder traffic to <LOCATION>Amsterdam Airport</LOCATION> .
