Kuwaiti oil minister <PERSON>Sheikh Ali al-Khalifa al-Sabah</PERSON> said <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> was producing well below its oil output ceiling and this would help prices move higher , according to a Kuwaiti newspaper interview .
The <ORGANIZATION>al-Rai al-Aam</ORGANIZATION> newspaper quoted him as saying <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> was pumping 2.4 mln barrels per day ( bpd ) less than its 15.8 mln bpd ceiling , while consumers were drawing down their petroleum stocks at a rate of 4.5 mln bpd .
As long as <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> maintains its output curbs , demand for its oil will rise in April and May , <PERSON>Sheikh Ali</PERSON> said , adding that <LOCATION>Kuwait</LOCATION> was strongly committed to its <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> quota .
