<ORGANIZATION>LSB Industries Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it entered into an agreement to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Northwest Federal Savings and Loan Association</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Woodward</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Oklahoma</LOCATION> .
Upon completion of the acquisition , <ORGANIZATION>LSB</ORGANIZATION> would pay about 1.5 mln dlrs to the shareholders of <ORGANIZATION>Northwest</ORGANIZATION> and transfer to <ORGANIZATION>Northwest Federal</ORGANIZATION> certain assets having a net current appraised value of not less than 30 mln dlrs .
At completion of this transaction , <ORGANIZATION>Northwest Federal</ORGANIZATION> would be a subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>LSB</ORGANIZATION> 's non-consolidated wholly-owned financial subsidiary .
The acquisition is subject to obtaining approvals , waivers and forbearances from the <ORGANIZATION>Federal Home Loan Bank Board</ORGANIZATION> and other government approvals .
