A spokesman for a group of <ORGANIZATION>United Airlines</ORGANIZATION> employees , who oppose the attempted takeover of <ORGANIZATION>United</ORGANIZATION> by the <ORGANIZATION>Airline Pilots Association</ORGANIZATION> , said he met with the new chairman of <ORGANIZATION>Allegis</ORGANIZATION> , <PERSON>Frank Olson</PERSON> .
<PERSON>William Palmer</PERSON> , the group 's spokesman , which claims to speak for thousands of <ORGANIZATION>United</ORGANIZATION> employees , said the meeting with <PERSON>Olson</PERSON> was " positive and friendly , " but no future meeting dates were set .
In April the pilots union offered to buy out <ORGANIZATION>United</ORGANIZATION> , an <ORGANIZATION>Allegis</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary , through an employee stock ownership plan .
