Brazilian Coffee Institute ( IBC ) president <PERSON>Jorio Dauster</PERSON> said he will not attend the <ORGANIZATION>ICO</ORGANIZATION> executive board meeting and was surprised to hear that a report of his absence had a slightly depressing effect on the <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> coffee market today .
" I have too much work to accomplish here in <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> at the moment .
Besides the presence of the <ORGANIZATION>IBC</ORGANIZATION> president at an <ORGANIZATION>ICO</ORGANIZATION> executive board meeting is not a tradition , " <PERSON>Dauster</PERSON> said .
<PERSON>Dauster</PERSON> said except in rare cases , <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> has always sent its <LOCATION>London</LOCATION>-based representative to <ORGANIZATION>ICO</ORGANIZATION> board meetings .
Ambassador <PERSON>Lindenberg Sette</PERSON> will attend the meeting , he said .
