<LOCATION>Swiss</LOCATION>-based <ORGANIZATION>Nestle S.A.</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Nestle Enterprises Ltd</ORGANIZATION> unit said it signed a letter of intent to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Nabisco Brands Ltd's Club</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Melrose</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Dickson</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Chase and Sanborn</ORGANIZATION> businesses for undisclosed terms .
<ORGANIZATION>Nestle</ORGANIZATION> said the final agreement , subject to required approvals , would be signed shortly .
The businesses involved in the deal provide products to hotels , restaurants and other parts of the food and beverage industry .
<ORGANIZATION>Nabisco</ORGANIZATION> is 80 pct-owned by RJR <ORGANIZATION>Nabisco Inc</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>RJR</ORGANIZATION> .
