<ORGANIZATION>Clorox Co</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Henkel KGaA</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Dusseldorf</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>West Germany</LOCATION> , agreed to increase its holdings in <ORGANIZATION>Clorox</ORGANIZATION> to 30 pct from the current level of 23 pct .
<ORGANIZATION>Henkel</ORGANIZATION> , which also holds a subordinated note convertible into another 1.7 pct of the company 's stock , intends to acquire the additional shares in the open market over an extended period of time , <ORGANIZATION>Clorox</ORGANIZATION> said .
It also said that , for the foreseeable future , <ORGANIZATION>Henkel</ORGANIZATION> does not intend to increase its participation in <ORGANIZATION>Clorox</ORGANIZATION> above the 30 pct level .
