<ORGANIZATION>Republic American Corp</ORGANIZATION> told the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> it raised its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Buckeye Partners L.P.</ORGANIZATION> to 963,200 limited partnership units , or 8.0 pct of the total , from 744,200 units , or 6.2 pct .
<ORGANIZATION>Republic</ORGANIZATION> , which is controlled by <LOCATION>Cincinnati</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Ohio</LOCATION> , financier <PERSON>Carl Lindner</PERSON> and his <ORGANIZATION>American Financial Corp</ORGANIZATION> , said it bought 219,000 <ORGANIZATION>Buckeye</ORGANIZATION> units between May 14 and 22 at prices ranging from 22.49 to 23.02 dlrs each , or about 5.0 mln dlrs total .
