<ORGANIZATION>Tribune Co</ORGANIZATION> said it exchanged cash and the assets of eight of its <ORGANIZATION>Sunbelt Publishing Co</ORGANIZATION> community publications circulated in the <LOCATION>Naples</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Fort Myers</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Fla.</LOCATION> , area for assets of nine community papers in suburban <LOCATION>Tampa</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>St. Petersburg</LOCATION> published by <ORGANIZATION>Gulf Coast Newspapers Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Gulf Coast</ORGANIZATION> is a subsidiary of the <ORGANIZATION>E.W. Scripps Co</ORGANIZATION> ( doing business as <ORGANIZATION>Scripps Howard</ORGANIZATION> ) .
No additional financial details were disclosed .
