<ORGANIZATION>C-I-L Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it would exercise its right to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Trimac Ltd</ORGANIZATION> 's stake in their jointly owned <ORGANIZATION>Tricil Ltd</ORGANIZATION> for 91 mln dlrs , with closing expected May 22 .
<ORGANIZATION>C-I-L</ORGANIZATION> added that the final price could be less , however , depending on an <LOCATION>Ontario</LOCATION> court ruling resulting from a previously reported legal action launched by <ORGANIZATION>C-I-L</ORGANIZATION> .
<LOCATION>Mississauga</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Ontario</LOCATION>-based <ORGANIZATION>Tricil</ORGANIZATION> is a waste management company with operations in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION> .
