The chairman of the <ORGANIZATION>Senate</ORGANIZATION> antitrust subcommittee said the <ORGANIZATION>Transportation Department</ORGANIZATION> was allowing too many airline mergers and proposed its authority be transfered to the <ORGANIZATION>Justice Department</ORGANIZATION> .
" The <ORGANIZATION>Transportation Department</ORGANIZATION> 's antitrust enforcement has been disastrous , permitting rampant merger mania , " <LOCATION>Ohio</LOCATION> Democrat <PERSON>Howard Metzenbaum</PERSON> said in a statement .
" The nine largest airlines now control 94 per cent of the market .
That 's bad for competition and bad for the consumer , " he said .
<PERSON>Metzenbaum</PERSON> said he introduced a bill to transfer antitrust authority over airline mergers to the <ORGANIZATION>Justice Department</ORGANIZATION> in hopes it would more restrictive than the <ORGANIZATION>Transportation Department</ORGANIZATION> .
