<ORGANIZATION>Merrill Lynch and Co Inc</ORGANIZATION> fired the head of the mergers department in its <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> office today , saying he had been unable to provide a " satisfactory explanation " in response to insider trading charges filed yesterday by the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Merrill</ORGANIZATION> had suspended the official , <PERSON>Nahum Vaskevitch</PERSON> , yesterday saying at the time it was " disappointed and angry " if the <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> charges are true .
<ORGANIZATION>Merrill Lynch</ORGANIZATION> 's statement at midday today said the firm will continue to cooperatie fully with authoriteis in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> investigating <PERSON>Vaskevitch</PERSON> 's activities .
