<ORGANIZATION>Colonial BancGroup</ORGANIZATION> said it acquired <ORGANIZATION>Farmers and Merchants Bank</ORGANIZATION> , a <LOCATION>Baldwin County</LOCATION> bank with assets of 103 mln dlrs , through an exchange of stock valued at about 12 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Colonial</ORGANIZATION> said it also signed letters of intent to acquire <ORGANIZATION>First Federal Bank</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Opelika</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Athens-Limestone Bank</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Athens</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Jackson County Bank</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Scottsboro</LOCATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Commercial National Bank</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Demopolis</LOCATION> , with aggregate assets totaling 130 mln dlrs .
