<ORGANIZATION>McGraw-Hill Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it bought <ORGANIZATION>Medecines et Sciences Internationales SA</ORGANIZATION> , a French Healthcare publisher , from <ORGANIZATION>Harper and Row Publishers Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
The sum of the deal was not disclosed .
It said the French company publishes original titles by French authors , as well as translations of American , British and German Medical books .
The company will be consolidated with <ORGANIZATION>McGraw-Hill</ORGANIZATION> <LOCATION>France</LOCATION> , it said .
