<ORGANIZATION>Carroon and Black Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it completed the acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>Poggi-Harrison Agency Inc</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Risk Control Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
Terms of the acquisitions were not disclosed .
Separately , <ORGANIZATION>Carroon</ORGANIZATION> said it also completed the acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>Rosskopf , Rapp and Schmidt Insurance Agency</ORGANIZATION> , based in <LOCATION>El Monte</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Calif.</LOCATION> .
