A <ORGANIZATION>Transworld Airlines Inc</ORGANIZATION> official said the airline has no comment on <ORGANIZATION>USAir Group Inc</ORGANIZATION> 's planned buyout of <ORGANIZATION>Piedmont Aviation Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>TWA</ORGANIZATION> , however , has pursued its application with the <ORGANIZATION>Department of Transportation</ORGANIZATION> for a takeover of <ORGANIZATION>USAir</ORGANIZATION> , according to <PERSON>Mark Buckstein</PERSON> , <ORGANIZATION>TWA</ORGANIZATION> general counsel and vice president .
<ORGANIZATION>TWA</ORGANIZATION> filed a revised application today , following the <ORGANIZATION>DOT</ORGANIZATION> 's rejection Friday of an incomplete application filed last week .
Earlier <ORGANIZATION>USAir</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to buy <LOCATION>Piedmont</LOCATION> for 69 dlrs cash per share .
