Industrial Equity ( Pacific ) Ltd , a <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> investment firm , said it raised its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Wrather Corp</ORGANIZATION> to 816,000 shares , or 11.3 pct of the total outstanding common stock , from 453,300 shares , or 6.3 pct .
In a filing with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Industrial Equity</ORGANIZATION> , which is principally owned by <ORGANIZATION>Brierley Investments Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , a publicly held <LOCATION>New Zealand</LOCATION> company , said it bought 362,700 Wrather common shares between Feb 13 and 24 for 6.6 mln dlrs .
When it first disclosed its stake in <LOCATION>Wrather</LOCATION> earlier this month , it said it bought the stock for investment purposes .
