<ORGANIZATION>Oppenheimer and Co</ORGANIZATION> , a <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> brokerage firm , said it raised its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Viacom International Inc</ORGANIZATION> to the equivalent of 2,709,600 shares , or 7.7 pct of the total , from 2,232,400 shares , or 6.3 pct .
In a filing with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Oppenheimer</ORGANIZATION> said it bought a net 477,200 <ORGANIZATION>Viacom</ORGANIZATION> common shares between Jan 19 and March 3 at prices ranging from 40.50 to an average of 49.31 dlrs each .
Part of its stake is in options .
It said it bought the shares as part of its arbitrage and investment business .
Movie theater magnate <PERSON>Sumner Redstone</PERSON> and a <ORGANIZATION>Viacom</ORGANIZATION> management group are in a bidding war for <ORGANIZATION>Viacom</ORGANIZATION> .
