<ORGANIZATION>Innovex Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it has completed the purchase of substantially of the interest in <ORGANIZATION>Lucht Engineering Inc</ORGANIZATION> that it did not already own .
Prior to this move <ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> owned 79 pct of <ORGANIZATION>Lucht</ORGANIZATION> , the company said .
<ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> said it bought the shares by exchanging 293,101 shares of unregistered <ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> common stock .
<ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> president , <PERSON>Thomas Haley</PERSON> , said the exchange is non-dilutive and will cause a slight increase in <ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> 's fully diluted earnings per share during the last half of fiscal 1987 .
<ORGANIZATION>Lucht</ORGANIZATION> will continue to function as a unit of <ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Innovex</ORGANIZATION> said .
