<ORGANIZATION>Upland Minerals and Chemicals Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Consolidated Brazilian Mines International Inc</ORGANIZATION> , a public company with one mln acres of diamond and gold properties in <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> .
Terms were not disclosed .
Consolidated owns 42 mining concessions in three regions of eastern and northern <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> -- <LOCATION>Gammara</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Santo Antonio</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Diamazon</LOCATION> , the company said .
<LOCATION>New York</LOCATION>-based <ORGANIZATION>Upland</ORGANIZATION> is traded over-the-counter .
