<ORGANIZATION>Industrial Equity ( Pacific ) Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , ( <ORGANIZATION>IEP</ORGANIZATION> ) the <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION>-listed unit of <ORGANIZATION>Brierley Investments Ltd</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>BRYA.WE</ORGANIZATION>, said it has lifted its stakes in British oil company <ORGANIZATION>Ultramar Plc</ORGANIZATION><ORGANIZATION>UMAR.L</ORGANIZATION> > and U.S. Firm < <ORGANIZATION>Ogelbay Norton Co.</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>IEP</ORGANIZATION> told the <ORGANIZATION>Stock Exchange</ORGANIZATION> it now holds 36.03 mln <ORGANIZATION>Ultramar</ORGANIZATION> shares representing 13.07 pct of the issued capital .
It holds 388,600 shares in <ORGANIZATION>Ogelbay</ORGANIZATION> representing 11.68 pct of the <LOCATION>Delaware</LOCATION>-based company .
No other details were available .
