<ORGANIZATION>Santa Fe Southern Pacific Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it has discussed with <ORGANIZATION>Henley Group</ORGANIZATION> that company 's almost five pct stake and was told the holdings are for investment purposes .
" We have confirmed with the <ORGANIZATION>Henley Group</ORGANIZATION> that they own approximately 7.9 mln shares of <ORGANIZATION>Santa Fe Southern Pacific</ORGANIZATION> common stock .
They have informed me that they like our company and purchased the stock last year for investment purposes , " <ORGANIZATION>Santa Fe</ORGANIZATION> chairman <PERSON>John Schmidt</PERSON> said in a statement .
Earlier <ORGANIZATION>Santa Fe</ORGANIZATION> 's stock was up 4-7/8 to 41 before slipping to be up 1-7/8 at 38 .
