<ORGANIZATION>Audio/Video Affiliates Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it will receive an undisclosed amount from <ORGANIZATION>Dixons Group PLC</ORGANIZATION> in connection with the termination of <ORGANIZATION>Cyacq Corp</ORGANIZATION> 's 92.50 dlr per share tender offer for <ORGANIZATION>Cyclops Corp CYL</ORGANIZATION> .
The company said the amount from <ORGANIZATION>Dixons</ORGANIZATION> is in lieu of reimbursement expenses for the <ORGANIZATION>Cyacq</ORGANIZATION> tender .
<ORGANIZATION>Citicorp CCI</ORGANIZATION> was the other partner in <LOCATION>Cyacq</LOCATION> .
The payment was in connection with <ORGANIZATION>Dixons</ORGANIZATION> ' previously - announced agreement to increase its tender price for <ORGANIZATION>Cyclops</ORGANIZATION> to 95.00 dlrs per share , <ORGANIZATION>Cycacq</ORGANIZATION> 's ending of its competing bid and the ending of litigation between the parties .
