<ORGANIZATION>United Jersey Banks</ORGANIZATION> said it plans to merge two of its southern <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> member banks into one 704 mln dlr organization .
It said <ORGANIZATION>United Jersey Bank/Fidelity Bank</ORGANIZATION> , based in <LOCATION>Pennsauken</LOCATION> , will be merged into <ORGANIZATION>United Jersey Bank/South</ORGANIZATION> in order to improve customer service and maximize efficiency throughout the southern <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> markets .
<PERSON>Raymond Silverstein</PERSON> , currently chairman of the board of <ORGANIZATION>United Jersey Bank/Fidelity</ORGANIZATION> , will be chairman of the merged bank , the company said .
