A group of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> investment companies told the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> they have acquired 173,000 shares of <ORGANIZATION>Moore-Handley Inc</ORGANIZATION> , or 6.9 pct of the total outstanding common stock .
The firms , <ORGANIZATION>Robert H. Barker and Co</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>J.M.R. Barker Foundation</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Quaker Hill Associates L.P.</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Upland Associates L.P.</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>James M. Barker Trust</ORGANIZATION> , said they bought the stock for two mln dlrs soley for investment purposes .
But the group said it might buy more <ORGANIZATION>Moore-Handley</ORGANIZATION> shares .
