<ORGANIZATION>UAL Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it completed the acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>Hilton International</ORGANIZATION> from <ORGANIZATION>Transworld Corp TWT</ORGANIZATION> , paying 982.5 mln dlrs in cash and securities .
<ORGANIZATION>Hilton International</ORGANIZATION> will add 90 hotels to <ORGANIZATION>UAL</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Westin</ORGANIZATION> hotel unit , which operates 61 hotels .
The two chains will have a total of 151 hotels with 67,000 rooms and 71,000 employees , it said .
<PERSON>Harry Mullikin</PERSON> , chairman and chief executive of <ORGANIZATION>UAL</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Westin Hotel</ORGANIZATION> unit , has been elected to the additional post of chairman and chief executive of <ORGANIZATION>Hilton International</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>UAL</ORGANIZATION> will change its name to <ORGANIZATION>Allegis</ORGANIZATION> at its annual meeting .
