<ORGANIZATION>British Petroleum Co PLC</ORGANIZATION> 's announcement that its <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> subsidiary intends to tender for the 45 pct of <ORGANIZATION>Standard Oil Co SRD</ORGANIZATION> it does not already own , catapulted <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> oil stocks sharply higher this morning , traders and analysts said .
" It raises the specter of additional consolidation in the industry and that is what is boosting the other oils , " analyst <PERSON>Rosario Ilacqua</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>L.F. Rothschild</ORGANIZATION> said .
<PERSON>Sanford Margoshes</PERSON> of <ORGANIZATION>Shearson Lehman Brothers</ORGANIZATION> said " this deal shows that <ORGANIZATION>British Petroleum</ORGANIZATION> , a conservative investor that knows the oil business , is clearly confident in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> oil industry , and that shines well on the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> companies " .
