<ORGANIZATION>Baird Corp BATM</ORGANIZATION> said the <ORGANIZATION>Massachusetts State Court</ORGANIZATION> for <LOCATION>Suffolk County</LOCATION> has lifted a temporary restraining order prohibiting <ORGANIZATION>Mark IV Industries Inc</ORGANIZATION> from further purchases of <ORGANIZATION>Baird</ORGANIZATION> stock .
<ORGANIZATION>Baird</ORGANIZATION> said the court also issued an order enjoining <ORGANIZATION>Baird</ORGANIZATION> from enforcing the <LOCATION>Massachusetts</LOCATION> Anti-Takeover Statute against <ORGANIZATION>Mark IV industries</ORGANIZATION> .
