<ORGANIZATION>Clabir Corp</ORGANIZATION> said its 86 pct owned affiliate , <ORGANIZATION>Ambrit Inc ABI</ORGANIZATION> , has agreed to acquire the <ORGANIZATION>Popsicle Industries</ORGANIZATION> division of <ORGANIZATION>Sara Lee Corp of Canada Ltd</ORGANIZATION> for about 37 mln Canadian dlrs in cash .
<ORGANIZATION>Clabir</ORGANIZATION> said the purchase from the <ORGANIZATION>Sara Lee Corp SLE</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary is worht about 28 mln U.S. dlrs .
The agreement is subject to Canadian regulatory approval .
<ORGANIZATION>Popsicle Canada</ORGANIZATION> , through its 19 licensees , is the largest maker and distributor of frozen novelty products in <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Clabir</ORGANIZATION> added .
