<ORGANIZATION>JP Industries Inc</ORGANIZATION> confirmed the announcement by <ORGANIZATION>Clevite Industries Inc CLEV</ORGANIZATION> that <ORGANIZATION>JP Industries</ORGANIZATION> has submitted a proposal to <ORGANIZATION>Clevite</ORGANIZATION> for the acquisition of the company at 13.50 dlrs per share in cash .
<PERSON>John Psarouthakis</PERSON> , chairman and president of <ORGANIZATION>JP Industries</ORGANIZATION> , said that the company hopes to promptly negotiate an agreement with the special committee of <ORGANIZATION>Clevite</ORGANIZATION> 's board .
In February , <ORGANIZATION>JP Industries</ORGANIZATION> said it purchased <ORGANIZATION>Clevite</ORGANIZATION> 's engine parts division .
<ORGANIZATION>JP Industries</ORGANIZATION> said it is not aware of any other reason for activity in its stock .
