<PERSON>Carlos Brasil</PERSON> , an adviser to the <ORGANIZATION>IBC</ORGANIZATION> president , said <PERSON>Dauster</PERSON> had left <LOCATION>Rio de Janeiro</LOCATION> for <LOCATION>Managua</LOCATION> early this morning .
There were rumours on the <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> coffee market earlier today that <PERSON>Dauster</PERSON> would not attend the meeting .
