<ORGANIZATION>Hecla Mining Co</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed to buy a 28 pct stake in the <ORGANIZATION>Greens Creek</ORGANIZATION> joint venture from <ORGANIZATION>Amselco Minerals Inc</ORGANIZATION> , a unit of <ORGANIZATION>British Petroleum PLC</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>BP BP North America Inc</ORGANIZATION> unit .
The <ORGANIZATION>Greens Creek</ORGANIZATION> venture is engaged in final project engineering of a gold-silver-lead-zinc ore body on <LOCATION>Admiralty Island</LOCATION> , about 15 miles southwest of <LOCATION>Juneau</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Alaska</LOCATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Hecla</ORGANIZATION> said it estimates its total investment in the project , including its share of production costs , will be about 45 mln dlrs .
