<ORGANIZATION>Cineplex Odeon Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it agreed in principle to acquire the <ORGANIZATION>Walter Reade Organization Inc</ORGANIZATION> <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> cinema chain from <ORGANIZATION>Coca-Cola Co</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Entertainment Holdings Inc</ORGANIZATION> unit for 32.5 mln U.S. dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Cineplex</ORGANIZATION> said the purchase price consisted of 22.5 mln dlrs cash and 652,742 <ORGANIZATION>Cineplex</ORGANIZATION> common shares .
The transaction is subject to fulfilment of certain unspecified conditions and regulatory and board approvals .
<PERSON>Walter Reade</PERSON> operates 11 screens in eight <LOCATION>Manhattan</LOCATION> locations .
