<LOCATION>Zimbabwe</LOCATION> 's projected coffee output of 13,000 tonnes for 1987/88 could be reduced by drought , growers said .
The main coffee growing areas in <LOCATION>eastern Zimbabwe</LOCATION> have received little rain since April 1986 and the <ORGANIZATION>Coffee Growers ' Association</ORGANIZATION> has begun a survey to assess the effects of the drought , a spokesman said .
<LOCATION>Zimbabwe</LOCATION> exported 11,000 tonnes of coffee in 1986 , mainly to <LOCATION>West Germany</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Britain</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> , the <LOCATION>Netherlands</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Switzerland</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> .
