<ORGANIZATION>Allegheny International Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it sold three overseas subsidiaries to <ORGANIZATION>Reil Corp Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , a <LOCATION>North Sydney</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Australia</LOCATION> , investment group .
Terms were not disclosed .
The units sold were <ORGANIZATION>Sunbeam Corp Ltd Australia</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Sunbeam New Zealand Ltd</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Victa ( U.K. ) Ltd.</ORGANIZATION> .
The units make and distribute various products , including lawn mowers , small appliances and sheep shearing equipment .
They employ a total of about 1,750 .
