<ORGANIZATION>Knight-Ridder Inc KRI</ORGANIZATION> said its <ORGANIZATION>TKR Cable Co</ORGANIZATION> joint venture with <ORGANIZATION>Tele-communications Inc</ORGANIZATION> has signed a letter of intent to acquire cable television systems with 55,000 basic subscribers in <LOCATION>Wildwood</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>N.J.</LOCATION> , and <LOCATION>Ramapo</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Warwick</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>N.Y.</LOCATION> , from <ORGANIZATION>Tele-Communications</ORGANIZATION> for undisclosed terms .
