<ORGANIZATION>Shamrock Capital LP</ORGANIZATION> said it has completed the sale of <ORGANIZATION>Cental Soya Co Inc</ORGANIZATION> to <ORGANIZATION>Ferruzzi Agricola Finanziaria</ORGANIZATION> the holding company for the <ORGANIZATION>Ferruzzi</ORGANIZATION> group of <LOCATION>Ravenna</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Italy</LOCATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Shamrock Capital</ORGANIZATION> is a limited partnership led by <ORGANIZATION>Shamrock Holdings Inc</ORGANIZATION> , the <PERSON>Roy E. Disney</PERSON> family company .
Under the agreement announced last month , <ORGANIZATION>Ferruzzi</ORGANIZATION> acquired all the equity and assumed subordinated term debt of about 195 mln dlrs in a transaction valued at about 370 mln dlrs .
