No action has been taken yet on the <ORGANIZATION>Reagan Adminstration</ORGANIZATION> 's offer to escort Kuwaiti oil tankers through the <LOCATION>Gulf</LOCATION> , but the issue is being discussed , U.S. Secretary of Defence <PERSON>Caspar Weinberger</PERSON> said .
The offer was made to <LOCATION>Kuwait</LOCATION> in light of <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> 's deployment of Chinese-built missiles to cover the entrance to the <LOCATION>Gulf</LOCATION> .
<PERSON>Weinberger</PERSON> told reporters prior to a speech at <ORGANIZATION>Texas Christian University</ORGANIZATION> that he did not think <LOCATION>Iran</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> were moving towards a potential conflict , adding that the <LOCATION>Straits of Hormuz</LOCATION> at the mouth of the <LOCATION>Gulf</LOCATION> were still " free water " .
