<ORGANIZATION>Conoco Inc</ORGANIZATION> , a subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>DuPont Corp</ORGANIZATION> , said it was increasing its contract prices for crude oil between 10 cts and one dlr a barrel , effective today .
<ORGANIZATION>Conoco</ORGANIZATION> said the increase brings its price for the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> benchmark crude <LOCATION>West Texas</LOCATION> Intermediate to 17.50 dlrs a barrel , up one dlr .
<LOCATION>South Louisiana</LOCATION> Sweet , also up one dlr , is now 17.85 dlrs .
<LOCATION>West Texas</LOCATION> Sour was up 10 cts to 16.60 dlrs a barrel .
<ORGANIZATION>Conoco</ORGANIZATION> was the last company to raise prices following a series of increases initiated last week by <ORGANIZATION>Sun Co</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>SUN</ORGANIZATION> , which reversed the posted price cuts made at the end of February .
