<ORGANIZATION>Condere</ORGANIZATION> , formed to acquire the <ORGANIZATION>Armstrong</ORGANIZATION> assets , said it named <PERSON>Dennis Terwillger</PERSON> , formerly vice president and controller of <ORGANIZATION>Armstrong</ORGANIZATION> 's Tire Division , president .
