<ORGANIZATION>Cyclops corp</ORGANIZATION> said it has reconstituted its board to include three <ORGANIZATION>Dixons Group PLC</ORGANIZATION> executives following <ORGANIZATION>Dixons</ORGANIZATION> ' acquisition of 83 pct of <ORGANIZATION>Cyclops</ORGANIZATION> ' 4,061,000 shares in a 95 dlr per share tender offer .
<ORGANIZATION>Cyclops</ORGANIZATION> said remaining on the six-member board are chairman and chief executive <PERSON>W.H. Knoell</PERSON> , president and chief operating officer <PERSON>James F. Will</PERSON> and senior vice president <PERSON>William D. Dickey</PERSON> .
