<ORGANIZATION>Delta Air Lines DAL</ORGANIZATION> said a court order requiring <ORGANIZATION>Western Air Lines WAL</ORGANIZATION> to arbitrate with two of its unions will not delay the April 1 merger between the two airlines .
The order , which was issued by the <ORGANIZATION>Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals</ORGANIZATION> , requires <ORGANIZATION>Western</ORGANIZATION> to discuss with its two unions whether <ORGANIZATION>Western</ORGANIZATION> 's labor contracts will be binding for <ORGANIZATION>Delta</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Delta</ORGANIZATION> said .
" Nevertheless , the court order could cause significant personnel problems , including the possible delay of wage increases <ORGANIZATION>Delta</ORGANIZATION> had planned to give the <ORGANIZATION>Western personnel</ORGANIZATION> on April 1 , " <PERSON>Ronald Allen</PERSON> , <ORGANIZATION>Delta</ORGANIZATION> 's president , said .
<ORGANIZATION>Delta</ORGANIZATION> said it feels the court has erred and should reconsider the order .
