<ORGANIZATION>AMR Corp</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>American Airlines</ORGANIZATION> unit said it plans to complete the integration of <ORGANIZATION>AirCal</ORGANIZATION> into its operations within four to five months .
<ORGANIZATION>American</ORGANIZATION> 's merger with <ORGANIZATION>AirCal</ORGANIZATION> , announced last November , received final approval from the <ORGANIZATION>Department of Transportation</ORGANIZATION> yesterday .
<ORGANIZATION>American</ORGANIZATION> said <PERSON>Richard D. Pearson</PERSON> , coordinator of the airline 's merger activities , will become chairman and chief executive officer of <ORGANIZATION>AirCal</ORGANIZATION> during the period up to completion of the merger .
<ORGANIZATION>American</ORGANIZATION> said <PERSON>Pearson</PERSON> succeeds <PERSON>William Lyon</PERSON> , who has been elected to <ORGANIZATION>AMR</ORGANIZATION> 's board .
