<ORGANIZATION>Hollinger Inc</ORGANIZATION> said 58 pct-owned < The <ORGANIZATION>Daily Telegraph PLC</ORGANIZATION> > , of <LOCATION>London</LOCATION> , agreed to form a joint venture printing company in <LOCATION>Manchester</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>England</LOCATION> with < <ORGANIZATION>News International PLC</ORGANIZATION> > .
Financial terms were undisclosed .
It said the deal involved <ORGANIZATION>News International</ORGANIZATION> 's acquisition of a 50 pct stake in the <ORGANIZATION>Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Trafford Park Printing Ltd</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary .
The joint company will continue to print northern editions of the <ORGANIZATION>Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Sunday Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> , with spare capacity used to print The <ORGANIZATION>Sun and News of the World</ORGANIZATION> .
The arrangement will significantly cut <ORGANIZATION>Telegraph</ORGANIZATION> costs , <ORGANIZATION>Hollinger</ORGANIZATION> said .
