<ORGANIZATION>Brooklyn Union Gas Co 's Brooklyn Union Exploration Co Inc</ORGANIZATION> unit said it entered a 200 mln dlr three-year gas and oil exploration and development venture with <ORGANIZATION>Smith Offshore Exploration Co.</ORGANIZATION> .
The agreement calls for drilling of 10 to 12 offshore wells per year , primarily in the <LOCATION>Gulf of Mexico</LOCATION> area off the <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Louisiana</LOCATION> coasts and 30 to 40 onshore <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Louisiana</LOCATION> Gulf Coast wells .
