<ORGANIZATION>Imatron Inc</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Mitsui and Co Ltd</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> has purchased a two mln dlr equity interest in <ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> at market price and was granted a 120-day option to make another two mln dlr investment at the same price .
<ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Mitsui</ORGANIZATION> , the exclusive importer of <ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> 's Ultrafast computed tomography scanners into <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> , is scheduled to take delivery of its first scanner next month for installation in a large cardiology center .
It said it has entered into preliminary discussions with <ORGANIZATION>Mitsui</ORGANIZATION> on the formation of a joint venture to finance the accelerated development of <ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> 's technology and its commercialization in <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> .
