<ORGANIZATION>Security Pacific Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it completed its planned merger with <ORGANIZATION>Diablo Bank</ORGANIZATION> following the approval of the comptroller of the currency .
<ORGANIZATION>Security Pacific</ORGANIZATION> announced its intention to merge with <ORGANIZATION>Diablo Bank</ORGANIZATION> , headquartered in <LOCATION>Danville</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Calif.</LOCATION> , in September 1986 as part of its plan to expand its retail network in Northern <LOCATION>California</LOCATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Diablo</ORGANIZATION> has a bank offices in <LOCATION>Danville</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>San Ramon</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Alamo</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Calif.</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Security Pacific</ORGANIZATION> also said .
