<ORGANIZATION>Microtel Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it has completed the acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>American Teledata Corp</ORGANIZATION> and its <ORGANIZATION>US Dial</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary , which provide long distance telephone service in <LOCATION>northeast Florida</LOCATION> .
Terms were not disclosed .
<ORGANIZATION>Microtel</ORGANIZATION> 's shareholders include <ORGANIZATION>Norfolk Southern Corp</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>NSC</ORGANIZATION> > , <ORGANIZATION>M/A-Com Inc</ORGANIZATION> < <ORGANIZATION>MAI</ORGANIZATION> > , <ORGANIZATION>Centel Corp</ORGANIZATION> < <ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> > , <ORGANIZATION>Alltel Corp</ORGANIZATION> < <ORGANIZATION>AT</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>E.F. Hutton Group Inc</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>EFH</ORGANIZATION> .
