<LOCATION>Montreal</LOCATION>-based <ORGANIZATION>Noverco Inc</ORGANIZATION> told the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> it reduced its stake in <ORGANIZATION>Sceptre Resources Ltd</ORGANIZATION> to 1,232,200 shares or 4.8 pct of the total outstanding .
<ORGANIZATION>Noverco</ORGANIZATION> said it sold off 400,500 shares " to reduce the investment of <ORGANIZATION>Noverco</ORGANIZATION> in <ORGANIZATION>Sceptre</ORGANIZATION> .
" " Additional common shares of <ORGANIZATION>Sceptre</ORGANIZATION> may be sold or purchased by <ORGANIZATION>Noverco</ORGANIZATION> , depending upon market conditions , " <ORGANIZATION>Noverco</ORGANIZATION> said .
