Non-Opec <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> produced 40.3 mln tonnes ( about 295 mln barrels ) of crude in 1986 against 44.3 mln tonnes ( about 323 mln barrels ) in 1985 , according to official figures released today by the <ORGANIZATION>Egyptian General Petroleum Corp.</ORGANIZATION> .
( <ORGANIZATION>EGPC</ORGANIZATION> ) .
Officials say <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> can produce up to one mln bpd per day , but production was cut when world prices plunged last year .
In an attempt to help <ORGANIZATION>OPEC</ORGANIZATION> stabilize the world market , <LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> cut its 1987 production target of 940,000 bpd to its current output of 870,000 bpd .
<LOCATION>Egypt</LOCATION> , which exports a third of its output , currently sells its top <ORGANIZATION>Suez</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Ras Bahar</ORGANIZATION> blends for 17.25 dlrs a barrel .
