<PERSON>Michael Krupp</PERSON> , a Golden , <LOCATION>Colo.</LOCATION> , businessman and major shareholder of <ORGANIZATION>Kappa Networks Inc</ORGANIZATION> , said he and <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION> 's management are considering seeking a merger between <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Radiation Systems Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
In a filing with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Krupp</ORGANIZATION> said companies he controls and <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION> acquired a combined 292,000 <ORGANIZATION>Radiation System</ORGANIZATION> shares , or 5.25 pct of the total .
<ORGANIZATION>Krupp</ORGANIZATION> , who has a 24.4 pct stake in <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION> , said he and <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION> management believe a <ORGANIZATION>Kappa</ORGANIZATION>-<ORGANIZATION>Radiation Systems</ORGANIZATION> combination would be good for both companies .
But no decision has been made on whether or how to proceed with a merger attempt , he added .
