<ORGANIZATION>Penril Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it is seeking to sell its <ORGANIZATION>Triplett Electrical Instrument Corp</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary in <LOCATION>Bluffton</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Ohio</LOCATION> , and <ORGANIZATION>Triplett 's Alltest division</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Hoffman Estates</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Ill.</LOCATION> , as part of a plan to concentrate on its three profitable division and reduce its debt load .
The company also said it is evaluating a plan to satisfy its obligations under its 10-7/8 pct subordinated notes but gave no details .
Interest on the notes is due today .
Penril further said director <PERSON>Clifford L. Alexander Jr.</PERSON> has resigned from the board .
It gave no reason .
<ORGANIZATION>Penril</ORGANIZATION> said shareholders at the annual meeting approved the limitation of directors ' liability .
