<ORGANIZATION>Schering-Plough corp</ORGANIZATION> said it is considering the sale of its <ORGANIZATION>Dr. Scholl</ORGANIZATION> 's businesses in <LOCATION>Europe</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Latin America</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>Far East</LOCATION> , which had sales of about 150 mln dlrs in 1986 .
The company said the transaction is not expected to have a material impact on earnings .
It said it has engaged <ORGANIZATION>Merrill Lynch and Co Inc MER</ORGANIZATION> to assist in the sale process .
<ORGANIZATION>Schering</ORGANIZATION> said it will retain <ORGANIZATION>Dr. Scholl</ORGANIZATION> 's businesses in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Puerto Rico</LOCATION> , which had sales of about 135 mln dlrs last year .
