Earthquake-stricken <LOCATION>Ecuador</LOCATION> is negotiating with <LOCATION>Nigeria</LOCATION> to have the African country lend it 10,000 barrels per day ( bpd ) of crude for export , Deputy Energy Minister <PERSON>Fernando Santos Alvite</PERSON> told <ORGANIZATION>Reuters</ORGANIZATION> .
He said <LOCATION>Ecuador</LOCATION> was negotiating a shipments schedule and the terms of repaying the loan .
<LOCATION>Ecuador</LOCATION> has suspended crude exports for about five months until it repairs a pipeline ruputured by a March five tremor .
<PERSON>Santos Alvite</PERSON> added <LOCATION>Ecuador</LOCATION> is finalizing details for a program under which <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> would temporarily lend the country 50,000 bpd for export .
