<ORGANIZATION>Gulf Canada Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it acquired a 25 pct working interest in the <LOCATION>Gulf of Suez</LOCATION> oil concession for undisclosed terms .
The company said its agreement with operator <ORGANIZATION>Conoco Hurghada Inc</ORGANIZATION> and <ORGANIZATION>Hispanoil</ORGANIZATION> covered the 168,374-acre <LOCATION>East Hurghada</LOCATION> offshore concession .
It said a 15.6 mln U.S. dlr four-well program was planned for 1987 .
After the acquisition , which is subject to Egyptian government approval , working interests in the <LOCATION>Hurghada</LOCATION> block will be Conoco <LOCATION>Hurghada</LOCATION> at 45 pct , <ORGANIZATION>Hispanoil</ORGANIZATION> 30 pct and <ORGANIZATION>Gulf Canada</ORGANIZATION> the balance .
