The <LOCATION>Peking</LOCATION>-owned China <ORGANIZATION>International Trust and Investment Corp</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>Citic</ORGANIZATION> ) bought the unfinished <ORGANIZATION>City Garden Hotel</ORGANIZATION> in <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> from a subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>Cheung Kong ( Holdings ) Ltd</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>CKGH.HKG</ORGANIZATION> for 235 mln H.K. Dlrs , <ORGANIZATION>Cheung Kong</ORGANIZATION> director <PERSON>Albert Chow</PERSON> said .
<ORGANIZATION>Cheung Kong</ORGANIZATION> 's subsidiary <ORGANIZATION>International City Holdings Ltd</ORGANIZATION> will complete work on the hotel by the end of 1988 , when it will be handed over to <ORGANIZATION>Citic</ORGANIZATION> .
The deal does not include the decoration or fitting out of the interior of the hotel .
The 600-room hotel stands on a 26,700 sq ft site on the eastern side of <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> island .
