This weekend 's meeting of Latin American coffee producers here will call for the <ORGANIZATION>International Coffee Organisation</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>ICO</ORGANIZATION> ) to start talks aimed at firming prices , Nicaraguan foreign trade minister <PERSON>Alejandro Martinez Cuenca</PERSON> said .
He said those countries which had confirmed their presence were <LOCATION>Brazil</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Mexico</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Guatemala</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>El Salvador</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Costa Rica</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Panama</LOCATION> .
<LOCATION>Colombia</LOCATION> had been invited but he did not know if it would attend .
<PERSON>Martinez Cuenca</PERSON> told reporters <LOCATION>central america</LOCATION> alone had lost some 700 mln dlrs through the weakness of world coffee prices , partially caused by lack of an <ORGANIZATION>ICO</ORGANIZATION> quota agreement .
