<ORGANIZATION>Parsow Partnership Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , an <LOCATION>Elkhorn</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Neb.</LOCATION> , investment partnership , said it bought a 5.1 pct stake in <ORGANIZATION>Orange-Co Inc</ORGANIZATION> common stock as an investment .
In a filing with the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Parsow</ORGANIZATION> said it had bought all its 220,000 <ORGANIZATION>Orange-Co</ORGANIZATION> shares in the open market with funds from its working capital .
The partnership , whose sole general partner is <LOCATION>Elkhorn</LOCATION> investor <PERSON>Alan Parsow</PERSON> , said it " has no present intention of effecting any change in the control of <ORGANIZATION>Orange-Co Inc.</ORGANIZATION>" .
