<ORGANIZATION>Peabody Holding Co Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it has completed its acquisition of substantially all <ORGANIZATION>Eastern Gas and Fuel Associate</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>EFU</ORGANIZATION> coal properties for 15.01 pct of <ORGANIZATION>Peabody Holding</ORGANIZATION> 's stock .
<ORGANIZATION>Peabody</ORGANIZATION> said the purchase includes seven underground mines and seven coal preparation plants currently operated by <ORGANIZATION>Eastern</ORGANIZATION> , as well as coal properties being mined by several contractors in <LOCATION>West Virginia</LOCATION> .
The acquisition also involves about 800 mln tons of coal reserves , mostly in <LOCATION>West Va.</LOCATION> , and includes <ORGANIZATION>Eastern</ORGANIZATION> 's coal reserves and inactive <LOCATION>Powderhorn</LOCATION> operations near <LOCATION>Palisade</LOCATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Colo</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Peabody</ORGANIZATION> said .
<ORGANIZATION>Peabody</ORGANIZATION> added that it expects to announce within the next week how it will staff and operate the properties and offices it has acquired from <ORGANIZATION>Eastern</ORGANIZATION> .
