The port of <LOCATION>Philadelphia</LOCATION> was closed when a Cypriot oil tanker , Seapride II , ran aground after hitting a 200-foot tower supporting power lines across the river , a <ORGANIZATION>Coast Guard</ORGANIZATION> spokesman said .
He said there was no oil spill but the ship is lodged on rocks opposite the <LOCATION>Hope Creek</LOCATION> nuclear power plant in <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> .
He said the port would be closed until today when they hoped to refloat the ship on the high tide .
After delivering oil to a refinery in <LOCATION>Paulsboro</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>New Jersey</LOCATION> , the ship apparently lost its steering and hit the power transmission line carrying power from the nuclear plant to the state of <LOCATION>Delaware</LOCATION> .
