<ORGANIZATION>Quaker Oats Co</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Keystone Partners Inc</ORGANIZATION> has purchased <ORGANIZATION>Vernell 's Fine Candies Inc</ORGANIZATION> , previously an indirect subsidiary of <ORGANIZATION>Quaker</ORGANIZATION> .
The price was not disclosed .
It said <ORGANIZATION>Vernell</ORGANIZATION> 's , based in <LOCATION>Bellevue</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Wash.</LOCATION> , had annual sales exceeding 30 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Vernell</ORGANIZATION> 's was acquired by <ORGANIZATION>Quaker</ORGANIZATION> in its acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>Golden Grain Macaroni Co</ORGANIZATION> in August 1986 .
