<ORGANIZATION>Caesars World Inc</ORGANIZATION> declined immediate comment on news that <PERSON>Martin Sosnoff</PERSON> 's < <ORGANIZATION>MTS Acquisition Corp</ORGANIZATION> > has held preliminary talks with two companies on the possibility of forming a joint venture to pursue the acquisition of <ORGANIZATION>Caesars</ORGANIZATION> .
Earlier today <ORGANIZATION>MTS</ORGANIZATION> said it held talks with <ORGANIZATION>Pratt Hotel Corp PRAT</ORGANIZATION> > and <ORGANIZATION>Southmark Corp</ORGANIZATION> < <ORGANIZATION>SM</ORGANIZATION> on forming a venture to acquire <ORGANIZATION>Caesars</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>MTS</ORGANIZATION> also reported that it received a " negligible " number of <ORGANIZATION>Caesars World</ORGANIZATION> shares in response to its 28 dlr per share tender offer .
Earlier this month <ORGANIZATION>Caesars World</ORGANIZATION> rejected the <ORGANIZATION>Sosnoff</ORGANIZATION> takeover bid and said it is considering alternatives that include a restructuring or sale of the company to another party .
