<ORGANIZATION>Air Canada</ORGANIZATION> , the state-owned airline , said it signed a letter of intent to acquire 65 pct of <ORGANIZATION>EMS Corp</ORGANIZATION> , a <LOCATION>Calgary</LOCATION>-based messenger service which operates in <LOCATION>Western Canada</LOCATION> and the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Gelco Corp</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>GEL</ORGANIZATION> ) earlier said <ORGANIZATION>Air Canada</ORGANIZATION> agreed to buy its Canadian <ORGANIZATION>Gelco Express Ltd</ORGANIZATION> unit for 54 mln U.S. dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Air Canada</ORGANIZATION> said the acquisitions will complement its main cargo business .
It said it expects the courier market to grow by about 25 to 30 pct a year .
