The amount of coffee stored in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> warehouses and certified for delivery against the <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> Coffee " C " futures totalled 585,555 bags as of April 3 , compared with 585,794 bags the previous week , a net decrease of 239 bags , the <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> <ORGANIZATION>Coffee , Sugar and Cocoa Exchange</ORGANIZATION> said .
The total comprised 392,845 bags in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> , an increase of 261 bags , and 192,710 bags in <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> , a drop of 500 bags .
The exchange said there were nil bags pending classification .
There were 56,578 bags pending certification , including 32,553 in <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> and 24,025 in <LOCATION>New Orleans</LOCATION> , the exchange said .
