A <ORGANIZATION>Mitsui and Co MITS.T</ORGANIZATION> spokesman said its subsidiary <ORGANIZATION>Mitsui and Co USA Inc</ORGANIZATION> bought two mln dlrs of newly-issued shares in <ORGANIZATION>Imatron Inc</ORGANIZATION> , an unlisted <LOCATION>California</LOCATION>-based medical equipment manufacturer .
<ORGANIZATION>Mitsui and Co USA</ORGANIZATION> is now <ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> 's fifth-largest shareholder with 3.1 pct of the firm 's outstanding shares .
<ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> is capitalised at 32.76 mln dlrs , the spokesman said .
<ORGANIZATION>Mitsui and Co</ORGANIZATION> intends to import <ORGANIZATION>Imatron</ORGANIZATION> 's computerised diagnostic equipment into <LOCATION>Japan</LOCATION> , he said .
