U.S. Attacks on two Iranian oil platforms in the <LOCATION>Gulf</LOCATION> -- both of which were still blazing -- caused damage estimated at 500 mln dlrs , <ORGANIZATION>Tehran Radio</ORGANIZATION> quoted Iranian Oil Minister <PERSON>Gholamreza Aqazadeh</PERSON> as saying .
The rigs , one of which was heavily shelled by four American destroyers on Monday , were still burning almost 24 hours after the attack and could cause widespread pollution in the <LOCATION>Gulf</LOCATION> , the minister told a news conference in <LOCATION>Tehran</LOCATION> .
He said the <LOCATION>Reshadat</LOCATION> rigs , 120 miles ( 200 km ) east of <LOCATION>Bahrain</LOCATION> in international waters , were in the final stages of reconstruction after an attack by Iraqi jets last year .
