One of a pair of private investors in <ORGANIZATION>Frost and Sullivan Inc</ORGANIZATION> told the <ORGANIZATION>Securities and Exchange Commission</ORGANIZATION> he increased his stake in the firm by about two pct , to 15.4 pct .
He is <PERSON>Theodore Cross</PERSON> , <LOCATION>Princeton</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>N.J.</LOCATION> , editor of Business and Society Review .
The other investor is <PERSON>Mason Slaine</PERSON> , <LOCATION>Cos Cob</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Mass</LOCATION> , president of <ORGANIZATION>Dealers ' Digest Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
He holds a 3.3 pct stake .
<PERSON>Cross</PERSON> told the <ORGANIZATION>SEC</ORGANIZATION> he bought the new shares at between 7.75 and 8.0 dlrs .
