<ORGANIZATION>Mobil Corp</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>MOB.N</ORGANIZATION> of the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Plans to open an office in <LOCATION>Peking</LOCATION> to develop oil exploration opportunities in <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> , the <ORGANIZATION>China Daily</ORGANIZATION> said .
It quoted <ORGANIZATION>Mobil</ORGANIZATION> president <PERSON>Richard Tucker</PERSON> , currently in <LOCATION>Peking</LOCATION> , as saying he is optimistic about investment prospects in <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> and that <LOCATION>Peking</LOCATION> will continue to encourage foreign private businesses to invest here .
It said <ORGANIZATION>Mobil</ORGANIZATION> bought 73 mln dlrs of crude oil and oil products from <LOCATION>China</LOCATION> in 1986 and sold it lubricant and fertiliser , but gave no more details .
