<ORGANIZATION>Aero Services International Inc</ORGANIZATION> said it signed an agreement with <PERSON>Dibo Attar</PERSON> , who controls about 39 pct of its common stock , under which three nominees to <ORGANIZATION>Aero</ORGANIZATION> 's board have been selected by <PERSON>Attar</PERSON> .
In addition to <PERSON>Attar</PERSON> , the nominees are <PERSON>Stephen L. Peistner</PERSON> , chairman and chief executive officer of <ORGANIZATION>McCrory Corp</ORGANIZATION> and <PERSON>James N.C. Moffat III</PERSON> , vice president and secretary of <ORGANIZATION>Eastover Corp.</ORGANIZATION> .
