<ORGANIZATION>Union Pacific Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it has closed the previously announced 50-50 partnership with <ORGANIZATION>Petroleos de Venezuela SA</ORGANIZATION> , <LOCATION>Venezuela</LOCATION> 's national oil company , to own a 160,000 barrel per day refinery in <LOCATION>Corpus Christi</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Texas</LOCATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Union Pacific</ORGANIZATION> said the partnership , called <ORGANIZATION>Champlin Refining Co</ORGANIZATION> , will acquire the refining and distribution system owned and operated by <ORGANIZATION>Union Pacific</ORGANIZATION> 's <ORGANIZATION>Champlin Petroleum Co</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary .
The Venezuelan company also signed a 25-year feedstock agreement with the partnership to supply at least 140,000 barrels a day of Venezuelan crude oil and naphtha at market related prices .
