<ORGANIZATION>Computer Network Technology Corp</ORGANIZATION> ( <ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> ) said that <ORGANIZATION>Quantum Venture Partners LP</ORGANIZATION> , a private investment limited partnership , has acquired an additional 600,000 shares of <ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> common stock , raising its stake in <ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> to 15.3 pct from 9.6 pct of the currently outstanding shares .
<ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> said <ORGANIZATION>Quantum</ORGANIZATION> bought the shares by exercising 1.5 mln dlrs in warrants , bringing its total investment in <ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> to 2.5 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>CNT</ORGANIZATION> also said <ORGANIZATION>Sand Technology Systems Inc</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION> bought two of its <ORGANIZATION>CHANNELink</ORGANIZATION> networking units for a data processing service for major health care facilities in <LOCATION>Canada</LOCATION> .
