<ORGANIZATION>Welbilt Corp</ORGANIZATION> said it acquired <ORGANIZATION>Food Handling Systems Inc</ORGANIZATION> of <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> , a producer of commercial ovens , conveyers and proofer systems .
Terms of the transaction were not disclosed .
<ORGANIZATION>Food Handling</ORGANIZATION> , which also produces equipment for the commercial baking industry , was privately owned by <PERSON>Richard Shumway</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Mesa</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Ariz.</LOCATION> , and <PERSON>Vic Ferrara</PERSON> of <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> , both of whom will remain with the company .
The company has manufacturing facilities in <LOCATION>Dallas</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Phoenix</LOCATION> .
