<ORGANIZATION>Ajinomoto Co Inc AJIN.T</ORGANIZATION> said it will sign around end-April to buy the 50 pct of < <ORGANIZATION>Knorr Foods Co Ltd</ORGANIZATION> > , capitalised at four billion yen , that it does not already own from its <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Partner <ORGANIZATION>CPC International Inc.</ORGANIZATION> .
<ORGANIZATION>Ajinomoto</ORGANIZATION> will also acquire 50 pct each of <ORGANIZATION>CPC</ORGANIZATION> 's two sales subsidiaries and six production units in <LOCATION>Hong Kong</LOCATION> , the <LOCATION>Philippines</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Singapore</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Malaysia</LOCATION> , <LOCATION>Taiwan</LOCATION> and <LOCATION>Thailand</LOCATION> , he said .
The total cost of the acquisition is 340 mln dlrs , the spokesman said .
