<ORGANIZATION>Teva Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd</ORGANIZATION> , based in <LOCATION>Israel</LOCATION> , said it sold its wholly owned <ORGANIZATION>Promedico</ORGANIZATION> subsidiary , to foreign investors for four mln dlrs .
It said the book value of the unit is about 2.2 mln dlrs .
<ORGANIZATION>Teva</ORGANIZATION> said it will continue to market <ORGANIZATION>Promedico</ORGANIZATION> 's products through its wholly owned subsidiary , <ORGANIZATION>Salomon</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>Levin and Elstein Ltd.</ORGANIZATION> .
