State-owned < <ORGANIZATION>Cie Generale d'Electricite</ORGANIZATION> > 's electrical contracting unit <ORGANIZATION>CGEE ALSTHOM</ORGANIZATION> has taken a 34 stake in the <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Computer firm <ORGANIZATION>ESCA Corp</ORGANIZATION> , <ORGANIZATION>CGEE ALSTHOM</ORGANIZATION> chairman <PERSON>Philippe Boisseau</PERSON> told a press conference .
According to an agreement in principle between the two companies <ORGANIZATION>CGEE ALSTHOM</ORGANIZATION> could take a majority stake in the future but no time-scale has been set , he added .
<ORGANIZATION>ESCA</ORGANIZATION> , which had a turnover of 13.6 mln dlrs in 1986 and is expected to see this rise to 20 mln this year , is one of the leading <LOCATION>U.S.</LOCATION> Suppliers of electric despatching and telecontrol systems .
